(Leonard:)Hi.
Hey, guys.
(Penny:)Hey.
Hi. There's the little family!
(Sheldon:)Hello.
Hello.
(Leonard:)And their Sherpas.
Mm-hmm.
(Howard:)The baby's asleep,
can we put her in your room?
(Penny:)Yeah. Go ahead.
Do you need help?
(Howard:)No. I got it.
(Howard:)Doubtfire, Poppins, follow me.
(Bernadette:)Sorry we're late.
(Penny:)Oh, it's no problem, Amy and
Sheldon were just telling us
(Penny:)about their trip to Texas.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. Here.
(Sheldon:)I'll catch you up.
(Sheldon:)How did we get in the car?
(Penny:)Stop.
(Penny:)Okay. They told Mary
they were living together,
(Penny:)there was a fight, he
got his feelings hurt,
(Penny:)then he put underwear
on his head...
(Leonard:)On purpose,
(Leonard:)not the way it used to
happen in high school.
(Sheldon:)I was acting odd
intentionally.
(Bernadette:)Really? So you can control it?
(Penny:)Okay. Then what happened?
(Sheldon:)Well, there's really
not much left to tell.
(Sheldon:)I decided that my mother
views me as a child